Okay, are we there? Oh my gosh, look at my hairline. I know Kate Kate was making fun of it again
And it isn't a pretty severe. I know I know
It's actually more but like an illusion because it's like not like it's like my that bald
I mean, I mean that looks terrible, but I don't know. I think it's the angle or something like that
Hi, how are you guys doing? Well, I got it started again. I don't know
Someone can send me a TTS
Because then I'll get drunk, and then I will
At least I'll buy a drink. I don't know. I won't get drunk. I had a coffee. I'm not a coffee
I'll just throw away the cups because you know, I don't go get free coffee or anything. Okay, um
Well, here I am here
Sorry, okay start recording. Okay, okay, so here we are review
I'm not sure if the chat is working correctly. Let me have a look at that
I didn't know this would be so complicated. I mean, it's oh my gosh. There you go
It's like make this full screen
Small, okay. I'm sorry guys. I'm still figuring this out. Let me just close this side
Hannah can I lower this I came
Why do you look there's shadow work on the screen me? I'll have to go to my regular age
Okay. Oh, hey, what's that big Rick? No speedo. What am I wearing?
Groovy death is here. Oh my god
Are you the guy on
There's like a guy on QE farms you froze you die now. I know
Your friends are like RG or something or is that another Jimmy death or something?
There's a groovy. I don't know
Are you in that gang?
My god, my face has been covered by these cards. Please no speedo. Yeah, it was a short stream, but I got it back on
so
Did something work did I hear like look at the coal energy at the level of the bottom?
It's we need more energy like hold on
Let me see if I can see mix this is the moon
Something again. Oh my god
the Empress
The energy that's reading is so intense. I'm not even doing a reading yet. What's going on here?
Hold on. Hi, rude. Okay. Let me fix it. Okay. That's all that's a little heart to you guys who gave me. I love it
I love it. I love it. Hold on. Okay. Um, I need to fix a couple things. Okay
Chat is not the real chat. Is it dummy chat? Not calling you guys dummies. I'm calling
Yeah, I'm gonna put the link up for the power chat too. It should it should read it aloud on the thing if not
I will use my best like Simpsons voice and do it if you have a song request
I will play that too, and I'll play the full songs tonight
If you donate the minimum or whatever
How'd you guys say I mean it's like it's been a kind of rough day. It's like, you know, it's one of those
Off the on again off again days, right?
But I hope everyone's okay. You don't have questions tonight. Okay
Okay, okay, let's not see this Jim is live
Fix it. Okay
Okay, tell me if you start seeing the real chats come in that's gonna be exciting part right when the real chat takes over the dummy chat
Oh, what's this gonna stream the wheel for you? Can I move that around? I mean, that's right in front of my face
Hello
On the screen is not even like that. It's like, it's like on the side. Oh, shit. I'm gonna break this.
Okay, let's do it. There we go. Okay.
So, I'm gonna go to my regular YouTube.
How are we doing? How are we doing?
Um, yeah, it's been a journey.
It's been a journey today, and it's like, it's not even like I can't like, you know, and I have other plans to like, to show other stuff.
So I'm gonna get drunk.
So I'm gonna test out the power chat just to see.
Okay, this can't be true. What why is everyone telling me you like turds? Oh
that's because
They're stupid and you listen to them
So you're gonna go on time out. Okay?
It can't be true
Well, I only like your mom's turds. Oh my gosh, is that inappropriate? I'm so sorry
anyway
anybody want to anyone interested in
Sponsoring McDonald's
We said we said to look on the screen see it looks different on that than it does on the
Regular YouTube it is blocking my face entirely. Oh, there he goes. It is blocking my face. Okay. Is that preferable?
I know I'm told I'm a scary-looking person sometimes
I'm really not okay. Well
Are the power shed alerts on?
Yeah, okay
Looks like they are
Is the overlay on?
Yeah
Oh, I just took it off.
Okay, there you go, there you go, that works.
Video capture device, is that on?
Oh, it disappeared, okay.
Well, it looks good.
Hail Psyche, I like that.
How about this, that comes on the screen all the time.
Okay, I think it looks decent, I don't know.
I'm working on it, this is a real chat coming in yet.
If we're just typing like crazy in the real chat,
let's get it like fired up so it starts like picking up
on the...
The real people is that there's like a lot of Easter eggs. I set up into it, too
There's also the tarot card of the day is a fool. That's a perfect one the first card. I
Love you see the other screen. Am I on the same level as you guys? Let me see
Check this out. Okay, there we go. Well, I mean, it's not ideal. It's seems like it's
On its way. Did we get a few TS yet?
I didn't hear them the cash register go up
What did it say? Hold on. Oh, it's me. He's making this bigger. Oh my god. I'm so sorry. I need to figure this out.
Hi Nancy. How are you sweetheart? Oh, shit. So yeah, well, we have an upheaval going on somewhere too, you know
There's gonna be readings. Let me see that the synchronicities are oh my god. It's above so below
Yep, those look like the right chats, right?
Love the community. Oh, thank you so much
Chat seems kind of nicer. Oh, hi. Oh, look at there. We got the moon
What are we peeking at? Please no speedo. I don't know the speedo is like, you know in the wash today
I have to wash it today. There's a death card coming. Oh, no. That's scary
Yeah, I don't know. There's gonna be some of this is gonna be too distracting
But um, if anyone has questions about the situation
You can probably TTS that
Otherwise
Yeah, I don't know. It's like unfortunate. It's like how much do I have in my account though, let me see
Maybe I can put forward like a kombucha or something
Let me see
But I didn't I don't know why my name is on some kind of extortion. It's like no, no, no, no, nothing like that
But maybe you can I leave that stream going like sort of another one at the same time
Okay, we'll see if the actually I don't know that's too complicated
Okay, let me just shut down this one
If you send a TTS, I'll get it on the on the left on this one. I didn't mean to put the alert link up
I think it's cold codex on me, but I don't know. I'm still working on it. Okay. I'll have to figure that out
I'll figure out tomorrow
but hopefully
You can have a good night, but I'm an hour and a half until the store closes. Okay. See you in a little bit